ILGWU. Central Pennsylvania District photographs 5780/090 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Central Pennsylvania District photographs
1941-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/090 P
9.67 cubic feet
7.17 linear ft.
Photographs.
This collection contains photographs documenting the activities of the members and staff of the Central Pennsylvania District. Included are photographs of union activities such strikes, rallies, meetings, and conventions, as well as classes, social gatherings, trips to Unity House, and others.
7128375
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 31, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kathryn Dowgiewicz, April 10, 2013
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States, the ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. In 1995, the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Biographical / Historical
Beginning in 1957 as the Central and Western Pennsylvania District, the Central Pennsylvania District was an affiliate within the ILGWU's Northeast Region. With the affiliate into two and renamed the Central Pennsylvania District and the Western Pennsylvania District by 1962, Central Pennsylvania District Council included four local unions (108, 170, 196, and 197) until 1987. From 1988 until the ILGWU's merger with ACTWU in 1995, the affiliate was reorganized as the Central and Western Pennsylvania and Reading District Council. During this period, the council included as many as eight local unions (98, 108, 170, 196, 197, 217, 424, and 445).
Martin Morand served as the district manager from 1957 to 1964. Edward Milano succeeded Morand, serving as Central Pennsylvania District manager until 1967. From 1967 to 1971, Sol Hofmann was manager. Ronald Aldman was the district's next manager, from 1971 to 1980. Jane Paluscio worked as manager from 1980 to 1985, followed by Ada Jakubic. When Jakubic passed away in 1993, Jay Levine assumed the position of manager of the Central and Western Pennsylvania and Reading District Council. Levine was manager of the affiliate at the time of the ILGWU's merger with ACTWU in 1995.
Throughout its existence, the Central Pennsylvania District Council worked closely with other affiliates in the Northeast Department, including local unions in Easton, Hazleton, Reading, Scranton, Shamokin, Sunbury, Pottstown, and Pottsville. By the 1960s, the ILGWU had established district councils in Scranton and Easton. In the 1970s, additional local unions were organized into the Shamokin-Sunbury District Council (185, 306), Hazleton District Council (225, 575), and the Wyoming Valley District Council (249, 327).
With the decline of manufacturing in the region in the 1980s and 1990s, these affiliates began to merge. The year 1986 saw the creation of the Shamokin-Sunbury-Pottsville District Council, and in 1990, the Scranton District Council was included in this affiliate. After 1988, the Hazleton and Wyoming Valley District merged.
Scope and Contents
The photographs in the collection provide a way to help illustrate the union at the local level. The images offer a look into the local unions and garment workers in Central Pennsylvania. While many of the photographs and negatives are not properly identified, most have some labeling. There is a wide range of formats, from oversize convention photographs, to rolled uncut 35 mm negatives, and numerous snapshots, often in their original envelopes. Subjects of the photographs include dinners, luncheons, meetings, events, retiree activities, holiday parties and dances, speeches and presentations, group shots of the members, dedications and anniversaries, exercise classes, rallies, demonstrations and strikes. There are also promotional images of the Mobile Health Center to advertise the type of health care and services offered to members.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/090: ILGWU. Central Pennsylvania District records
Women's clothing industry -- United States.; Women's clothing industry -- Pennsylvania.; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States.; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania.; Clothing workers -- United States.; Clothing workers -- Pennsylvania.; Industrial relations -- United States.; Industrial relations -- Pennsylvania.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union -- Photographs.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. -- Central Pennsylvania District -- Photographs.
7128375
- Rolled negatives, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes: Lancaster party, Kissel Hill retirees, 1973; Belle, Seattle, Hawaii; Harrisburg; Retirees - Lancaster trip Unity Institute delegates; Humphrey, 1968; Union Label Convention, 1970; Election payoff; Retirees - Christmas; Lebanon Christmas party; Convention, civil rights, 1968; Belle - Debra; unlabeled
- Rolled negatives, 1967-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Includes: Shop council, York, Harrisburg; Shriver, Sol 1967; Hawaii, 1973; Terrie Anne [illegible], York class, symphony; York retirees - COPE awards; Human relations; Blouse negotiations - Terry shop; Allegheny District Council, 1967, 1970; political big shots, Harrisburg, 1970; York shop council, retirees; hay ride, York shop council, 1966; political state committee; district council, 1970; Allenberry; Christmas party, 1973, Retiree birthday party, Opryland, Harrisburg; Metro opera, Hobby trip New York, June 1970; CLC class, retirees class, Crall meeting, LP retiree; Lebanon retirees, Parke's [?], 1968; Belle Scott, Unity House; Shriver; Lancaster shop council; Yorkana, 1967; York; Christmas; President Johnson; Lancaster; Union Label; conferences; Justice; York shop council; Lancaster shop council with Gingold; Birch Bayh, 1970; State capital conference, Harrisburg, February 1976; Lancaster-York Christmas party, 1973; HAAC institute, May 1973; Harrisburg shop council, October 1973, retirees; DiAnne; retirees; Democratic rally, Ted Kennedy, 1967; Quarter DR[?], York Retirees with Eater things and doll; Retirement staff; Grantham, Pittsburgh; unlabeled
- Mixed negatives (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Includes: Union Label; H and W [Health and Welfare], AFL-CIO, York, Local 225, William Bern; DiAnne, Christmas party; Risser; Christmas parties, Lancaster class, Treasurer, York Executive Committee; DiAnne group; Retirees; unlabeled
- Mixed negatives (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Includes: York; Dem [Democratic?] dinner, 1966; Dallas tour, Msville; York County Labor Council [parade float]; mother, dad; Philadelphia COPE, 1966; Christmas, 1966; Washington trip and ? And Udall; Childrens dress; Sol (miscellaneous); Harrisburg Christmas party; den motherr [?], York officers; Washington - Kennedy; NY AFL-CIO
- Mixed negatives, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Includes: press dress [?]; Unity House, 1964; Union Label, Esther Peterson; sewing needles; Blatt, UC [unemployment compensation?] UC protest; Judy Bond, York, Peterson; blood bank; Ted Kennedy, Unity House, 1968; Allegheny District Council, 1965; Union Label, 1965; Education Institute, Pennsylvania State University, 1965; Lancaster shop council, 1969; Negotiations, LPC, Jewel Togs, 1965; Cameron Dress retireers, Lancaster, Christmas party; Ted Kennedy; Lancaster class
- Mixed negatives, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Includes: Lancaster Education Committee; me, mayor, Union Label; District Council Allenberry; CLC Picnic; HP ratification; deceased and retirees, 1965; Kline Union Label; untitled
- Mixed negatives, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Includes: Tidy with Sol, Marty farewell; COPE, D/C; York, Lancaster, Bern Hanes [?] committtees, shop project; York brownies; Judy Bond, Pomeroys, 1965, Aud. Committee, CLC picnic; community service; AFL-CIO convention; Union Label ad; Election shop council; retirees
- Mixed negatives, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Includes: Christmas party, 1965; Cameron Dress; community service; Lancaster Education Institute; Harris, U/E, capital; scholarship; classes; HCLC class, retirees, Gingold swearing in; Sol's election; Book pic, severance; Croley with pet; Milano, installation, C/ ballots, book rack; Lancaster class and graduation; Community service committee Christmas party, York, 1965; flu shots; untitled
- Mixed negatives (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Includes: Class, Pennsylvania State University; unemployment compensation; Christmas, Williamstown; Singing Needles; Weiss Market; Belle [illegible] Dress; Harrisburg retirees; unemployment compensation, Allenberry, Weiss, Singing Needles; Ralph press conference
- Mixed negatives, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Includes: Lancaster classes, 1965; retirees; Milton Shapp, retirees; unemployment compensation; Marty farewell; African students, Cameron Dress
- Mixed negatives, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Includes: Hilda [?]; community service; Washington; picket line; building sane students, Allenberry, scholarship committee, scholarship winner, Med. Art dedication; Zimmerman Christmas party; Christmas party, 1964; Local Labor Co [College? Council?]; personal; miscellaneous; untitled
- Mixed negatives, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Includes: unemployment compensation, York strike; COPE legislative conference, Lancaster shop council, 1963; Freedom March, library award, Penn Garment Manufacturing, Clay [?] Institute; Bannon Mills; Yorktown retirees, Penn State conference; Unity House, Executive Committee, 1963; community service; Enders - political, Union Label and Harrisburg, Dress Joint meeting, Wilkes-Barre; Marty and family; Columbia meeting, Shopp; York strike; Maytown class, York fair; Christmas pary, Lebanon, 1963; Christmas party, Harrisburg, 1963, staff - office; untitled
- Mixed negatives (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Includes: York, Reading; my house and farewell; Unity [House?]; community service; farewell dinner, parents home; DR Bloom, Allenberry; strike meeting, vote; Penn State; retiree; Marvin [?] farewell; classes; political, York class; retireer, district council; conference; staff classes; untitled
- Building committee meeting, scholarship committee meeting (same meeting), Allenberry, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Child-dress (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Christmas, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Christmas, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- District Council (Box 3, Folder 16)
- [Dancing] (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Ephrata Fair, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- [Exercise] (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Farm Coalition, Birch Bayh (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Flood (Box 3, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Green campaign for Senate (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Harrisburg Centennial, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  September 1960
- Harrisburg shop council (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Harrisburg shop council, York shop council, Venture (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Health care (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Health care, Mobile Health Unit, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Health care (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Hesteco (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Hubert Humphrey/Bayard Rustin (Box 3, Folder 31)
- ILGWU Bonnie Segal [includes voting] (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Institutes (Box 3, Folder 33)
- [International Labor Press Association, Atlantic City, New Jersey] (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Judy Bond, Merry Mites strikes, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Local 93 - Christmas and 1986 office, dinners, and public action (Box 3, Folder 36)
- MLK Jr. Memorial (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Mary V. anniversary, retiree picnic (Box 3, Folder 38)
- [McGovern/Shriver] (Box 3, Folder 39)
- McGovern, retirees (not used) (Box 3, Folder 40)
- National Council of Senior Citizens (Box 3, Folder 41)
- New York, Bob H. organization, Lancaster shop council, retirees, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  February 1966
- New York City (Metropolitan Opera, Triangle fire site) (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Penn State class, Gus Tyler, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO classes, district council, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO legislative drive (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO legislative drive (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO legislative drive (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Picnic, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Political committee (Box 3, Folder 50)
- [Protest] (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Rally [Burke-Hartke Bill] (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Retirees (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Retirees, Scranton coal mine (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Retirees - York; shop council (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Rutgers (Box 3, Folder 56)
- [Sargent/Shriver] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Scholarships (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Schwenker [?], Spur, Beth (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Milton Shapp (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Shapp inauguration (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Shop councils (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shop and council meetings (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Staff institute (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Union Label (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Union Label, Rochester; Atlantic Labor Press Conference (Box 4, Folder 10)
- United Nations tour, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Washington, D.C. visit, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Washington, D.C. tour, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- World's Fair (Box 4, Folder 14)
  1964 or 1965
- York, Lebanon (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Mixed photographs, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Includes: convention (?); classes, Local 196; basketball team; film party, 1952, baseball
- Mixed photographs, 1949-1958 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Includes: shop council meeting, 1949; Allenberry, 1958
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Includes: performance, health care, Lykens Dress Joint Council "won't scab"
- Mixed photographs, 1941-1949 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Includes: "Living on $20," "We won't scab," Lykens Dress; health care; Unity House
- Mixed photographs, 1950-1957 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Includes: health care, leafletting at William Noggle; retirees; 1950 convention; sewing Union Label
- Mixed photographs, 1945-1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Includes: "Gold Star Mother;" Local 108 Quaker Maid strike; JFK, 1960; David Dubinsky
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Includes: convention, health care, Civil Defense Emergency vehicle, IGWU
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Includes: Harry S. Truman election; mental health; minimum wage
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Includes: mental health, minimum wage, John F. Kennedy, health care
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Christmas, officers, celebrations
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Local 108 officers, other officers; 1958 strike rally, Zembo mosque; Capital Classic; Hanover Manufacturing
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Includes: Local 108, Harrisburg
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Includes: Local 196 strike; disbabled workers; Fair Employment Practices Commission
- Mixed photographs, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Includes: 1958 United Nations tour, Washignton, D.C.; Fair Employment Practices Commission
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Includes: protest, "Scranton unfair to disabled workers;" health care; Philadelphia
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Includes: portraits; group photographs; Philadelphia
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Includes: Hubert Humphrey supporters; group photos; swearing-in; reading
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Includes: Local 197 officers; scholarships; Union Label dresses; presentation of Leon Stein's The Triangle Fire; Union Label week; swearing-in; counting ballots
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Includes: Union Label dresses; workers in shop; group photos
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Includes: convention; Tidy Products Company strike; group photos
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Includes: meetings; Christmas party; Martha McCormick, Harriet Mark; Irwin Solomon, Ricco Guerino
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Includes: meetings; Tidy strike; "With These Hands" marquee; workers in shop
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Includes: severance pay; candidates; Vera de Benedetto, Mary Scardle, Violet March, Melvin Eshleman; Mary Kramer, Verla Williams; Betty Harmuth, Velma Perini; President Ethel Garber, Secretary Thelma Martin, Treasurer Jennie Frederic, Local 197, 1956; Charlotte Krause, Emma Mackey, Margaret Long; Teresa Kline; Sol Chaikin with group
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Includes: retirees; volunteers for picket duty; Orphanage of Kenitra, 1960; Di-Anne Sunshine Club, AFL-CIO; party
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Includes: Union Leadership Training School; Sol Chaikin; party
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 41)
  Includes: classes [Union Leadership Training School?]; Sol Chaikin
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 42)
  Includse: Lykens Dress meeting; protests; collection for Tennessee sharecroppers
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 43)
  Includes: workers in shop; group photos; Evelyn Sichwire, Alice Hale, Rachel Knight, Mary Fry, Marion Rozoff, George Lepperd
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 44)
  Includes: Union Label; scholarship; Capital Dance, Hawaii; district council; Press Dress; COPE Philadelphia; Elma Ross, me, New York; Christmas party; shop council, Washington, Sol, retirees; Harrisburg shop council; New York
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Includes: Senior citizens, chairlady, blouse negotiations; Union Label; Unity House, Belle Scott classes, 1967; Belle Scott, community service, officers; press; shop council
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 46)
  Includes: York shop council; retirees; award; Lancaster shop council; Kennedy; York chorus-shop council, Shopp housing
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Includes: meetings; Lydon B. Johnson; workers in shops
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 48)
  Includes: meetings; swearing-in; Louis Stulberg, Sol Chaikin
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 49)
  Includes: meetings; group photos; Senator Clark
- Mixed photographs (Box 4, Folder 50)
  Includes: "Right to Work;" party; workers in shop; meeting
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Includes: Toys for Tots
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Includes: Children's Christmas party, Manager Rotell with children and Santa; Labor Council, food drive, Toys for Tots; pictures from Local 93, Christmas party, food basket drive; retirees club selilng chances at Local 93 Christmas party; children's Christmas pary committee and Santa; Allure strike
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Includes: rally, Washington, D.C.; Lyndon B. Johnson
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Includes: party, Christmas with Santa, protest "Roll Back Imports"
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Includes: Christmas, meetings, dinners, protest "Roll Back Imports," Local 93, protesters in front of David Crystal Children's Division
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Includes: dinners, Christmas with Santa, protests "Veto the Veto," protesters outside of David Crystal Children's Division
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Includes: fair, fashion show, celebration
- Mixed photographs, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Includes: Christmas with Santa; Windsor Knitting Mill, Edenburgh, Pennsylvania; Unity House, 1989; picnic, Evergreen Country Club, August 12, 1989; Crystal strike, 1898; retirees rally, Harrisburg, mom rally and meeting, 1989; graduating class from Votech [?] by PIC, 1989
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Includes; Christmas; food drive; meetings; office; United Labor Council of Reading and Bucks County; rally in Philadelphia
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Includes: Allenberry; Terre Hill, [illegible], blouse negotiations, Oxford Blouse; Pittbsurgh, Terre Hill; Nettie Frocks, Quaker strike, Newport, backpay, [Gravillian?] severance; office; Christmas parties
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Includes: Sol Chaikin, party, meeting, Unity House
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Includes: Local 108, Local196
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Includes: Central Pennsylvania District at Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW) meeting
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Includes: meeting
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Includes: meeting, voting, workers in shop
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Includes: Pennsylvania Council of the Union Label and Service Trades Council; food drive [?], campaigning for Milton Shapp
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Includes: Sargent Shriver event, Christmas crafts
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Includes: TWA flight, meeting
- Mixed photographs, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Includes: trip to the Strand Motel, Atlantic City, June 24th, 1970
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Includes: meetings
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Includes: meetings at Hershey Motor Lodge and Convention Center and Host Town Motel, event at stadium
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Includes: Christmas party
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Mixed photographs, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Includes: meetings; rallies; Penn State Labor Institute, 1947-1948
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Includes: Louis Stulberg event; workers on strike at Nette Frocks; workers on strike at MiJan Fabric Company; meetings
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Includes: meetings, Christmas greetings, community service conference
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Includes: meetings, strikers, David Dubinsky, vacation
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 29)
  Includes: meetings; crafts; Bonnie Segal; ULA graduation, 1972; leafletting; Campaign Award to Cameron Dress Company; scholarships [?]; dinner; flooding
- Names, addresses, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Includes: Church [illegible]; M Zimmerman; District Council Executive Committtee; Kline-Lebanon, Mary Keller family, 1971; Institute; Cameron Dress United Fund; Harrisburg S/C meeting; Union Label District, Lancaster; Penn State COPE Institute
- Names, addresses, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Includes: Penn State, scenery, Elections, retirees, Unity House, 1974; ILG day; R. Reuther [?] offices; Institute; shop council meetings, senior citizens; extras
- Names, addresses, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Includes: community service, classes; Local 108 election, 1977; conference
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Includes: Christmas party; protesting Judy Bond; picketing to support meat cutters; Union Label Week; meetings; striking Pramco Blouses
- Mixed photographs (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Includes: meetings; signings; health care; petitions to "stop exporting jobs and importing unemployment"
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Includes: Local 108, 196, 197 registration drive; union bakers display; Shapp-Kline event; Labor USO; Christmas party, Lancaster Moose Club, November 29, 1957; Local 108 dance for servicemen, Zembo Mosque, November 1941
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Includes: recreation, meetings
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Includes: nutrition lesson; meeting; United Way service award; Burke-Hartke Bill organizing
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Includes: meetings, Christmas parties
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Includes: Unity House
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Includes: recreation, Local 196 retirees
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 7)